（ニャムサス）さむッ
Brrr!
≪（加奈子）お～ッ
I'm on my way home from a job interview.
≪（加奈子）いや～
バイトの面接の帰りでさ→
Eat all you want. It's on me.
遠慮すんなよ　おごりだ
ニャ～ッ
（加奈子）けどデッカくなったよな
マジで
Anyway, you've gotten really big.
覚えてっか？　ホラ→
Do you remember me?
I used to play with you a lot.
ガキの頃　よく遊んでやったろ→
潤平のヤツ　アレルギーあって…
Junpei was allergic to cats, so...
ニャ～
でも　よかったぜ
Anyway, I'm glad I ran into you again.
また　こんなふうに
会えるようになって
じゃあ　またな
See ya.
〈それは私とかい？
それとも　あのヘタレとかい？〉
Me, or that useless doofus?
〈潤平のヤツ
一体どうするつもりかね〉
I wonder what Junpei is planning to do...
〈いろいろと…〉
about everything.
ano sora e kimi to hashiri dasou
I'll dash towards the sky.
negaigoto zenbu kanaete ageru...
I'll make all your wishes come true.
areya koreya to oshiyosete
Troubles engulfed me at every turn,
itsuno manika nichijou goodbye
and my normal days were gone before I knew it.
anote konote neko tedasuke
I help the cats with this and that.
guruguru mawaru triangle
The triangle whirls around me.
ukauka shite rarenai
There's no time to waste.
isoganakya ikenaitte
I'd better hurry.
kimi eno omoi mo sou nandaka karamawari de
My feelings towards you are spinning in circles.
tsuite nai koto mo
An unfortunate event
ookina chance ni naru kamo shirenai!
might prove to be a big opportunity!
kimi no egao ga mireta nara kitto
If I get to see your smile,
nyan toka narutte mae wo mukeru yo
I'll try to believe everything will be fine.
masa ni nyanderful
It's really a wonderful cat power.
itsuka kono te todokimasu you ni
May this hand reach you some day.
negaigoto zenbu kanaete miseru yo
I'll really make all your wishes come true.
Cat 11!
Friends
Ow.
（潤平）アチッ！
Oh? Got a cat's tongue now?
Note: In Japan, "cat's tongue" is an idiom for sensitivity to hot food.
（鈴）あれ？　猫舌だったっけ？
まあな
Y-Yeah.
Even though he hates cats, he's at that age.
（静江）猫嫌いのくせに
お年頃だからねえ
That's totally unrelated!
関係ないよね
Young man, do you want me to blow on your food?
お年頃さん　フーフーして
あげようか　フーッ　フーッ
By the way, how are things going with that girl?
≪（静江）そういえば　あの子とは
その後どうなってんだい？
"That girl"?
あの子って？
The girl you think of right before you fall asleep.
寝る直前に思い出す子
Dad was concerned too. He wrote about it in his letter.
父さんも心配して
手紙に書いてたわよ
"So, who is Junpei really after?"
「で　結局潤平の本命は
誰なんだ？」って
What are you telling him while he's away?!
何　知らせてんの！？
単身赴任先まで
ニャ～
Why are you looking at me so funny?
〈んだよ　お前まで　そんな目で〉
You can see that I'm busy right now.
〈分かってんだろ　俺は今
それどころじゃねえっつの〉
アチッ！
Ow.
Yes, my tongue's like a cat's now because of the curse, obviously.
〈そう　俺がいきなり
猫舌になったのは〉
〈もちろん呪いのせい〉
It happened after someone found out that the cat statue was broken.
〈猫地蔵が壊れてんのが
ついにバレちまって以来だ〉
You need to pay your monthly bill in full, Mr. Monk.
《（キャバ嬢）今月のツケ
払ってもらいたいんだけど》
《住職さん》
I-I'm not a monk.
《（住職）わしゃ
住職じゃないトゥース！》
I'm actually in the IT industry—
《こう見えて　ＩＴカンケーの…》
But you smell of incense.
《でも線香の　においするし～》
Wh-Wh-What are you talking about?
《な　な　なッ　何のことかな？》
《しまった！》
Oh no!
Th-This is...
《これは…》
《タイヘーン！》
Oh boy!
《オッホン…》
《ぜひ檀家の皆さんに
お志をお願いしたいのじゃが…》
I must ask you faithful supporters for a donation.
You need to stop going to cabarets!
《まずキャバクラ通いを
やめなさいよ　あんたが》
You lazy monk!
《この　なまぐさ坊主ッ》
《週８はヤバイぞ》
Eight times a week is beyond excessive!
Right now they blame the monk for breaking it.
〈壊したのは住職ってことに
すっかりなってる〉
But actually...
〈けどホントは…〉
it was me.
俺　なんだよな
（晴彦）うん？　何か言った？
Did you say something?
えッ　いや　別に…
Nothing.
そっか？
Oh.
〈正直に白状すべきか…　けど
完璧にタイミング逃しちまったし〉
Should I tell him the truth?
But I totally missed my opportunity.
≪（凪）では　めでたく２学期を
終えられたことを祝して→
Let's celebrate the peaceful completion of our second term.
Cheers!
乾杯！　ジュースで
With juice!
Cheers! With juice!
（一同）乾杯！　ジュースで
Tutankhamun!
（爺）ツタンカーメン
入ります　丁　半！　丁　半！
Here we go!
Go! Go!
（楓）ああ～ッ　先輩が
グサグサのバラバラ…
Senpai's been poked full of holes and—
しっかりしろ　楓
Hang in there, Kaede!
Everything's in place now!
丁半　そろいました
This is a great time
いい機会だ　ここからは
凪様オンステージを見せてやる
for me to put on a show for you.
Miracle Power!
I'll go run on the track!
How's he been since then?
どうよ？　その後
Not good.
（朱莉）ダメ　ウチの寺
最近おっきな買い物したばっかで
The temple recently spent a lot of money.
（琴音）お金ないのです
So he's flat broke.
地蔵様は怒っておられます
こないだの　まねき猫と同じく
The statue is mad, just like the manekineko from the other day.
But why is it punishing me?
なにも俺に八つ当たりしなくても
The mood's pretty bad over there.
なんか暗いね　高坂君達
Yeah...
Anyway, show your feelings through dedication.
とにかく　せめて
気持ちを誠意で示しなさい
Show that you're a man!
男だったらシャンとして！
はい…
Y-Yes.
えッ？
気持ちって？
His feelings?
ウイーッ　コラ　お前達
しんきくさい顔しおって
Whassup, you guys?
Lose the serious faces!
飲めッ　騒げッ
Come on, join the party!
…って何で真っ赤？
Why are you so flushed?!
お嬢様はジュースで
ハイになられてしまう
Ojou-sama has a very unique condition. She gets plastered on normal juice.
特異な体質なのです
高坂　やはり気は変わらんのか？
Kousaka...
You haven't changed your mind?
私をめとれば
この屋敷もファラオのひつぎも
If you take me as your wife, both this house and the Pharaoh's coffin will be yours.
すべて　お前のものに…
I-I don't want them!
いや　いらないし
ちょっと何デレデレしてんのよ
You there! Stop being soft on her!
Hey, Koubaka! You're really having fun talking with her, huh?
へえ～　おもしろそうな
話してんじゃん　高バカよお
Don't just stand there, help me!
見てないで助けろッ
S-Senpai...
先輩…
おおッ　楓　今日も美しい
Oh! Kaede!
You're beautiful again today.
Oh my, Japanese drama!
ワオッ　ジャパニーズ修羅場
With dedication, huh...
〈誠意を示せか…
まッ　確かにそのとおりだな〉
Well, she's right.
〈よしッ！〉
Okay!
あの～　すいません
はい
Excuse me.
Yes?
アルバイトの募集してるって
聞いたんすけど…
I heard that you're hiring additional help.
Junpei-kun!
（千鶴）潤平君！　ようこそ
Welcome!
見てくれたんだ　私のラブレター
So you saw my love letter?
ちょッ…
こういうの勘弁してくださいよ
Stop playing tricks!
ウチの女どもに
またいろいろ　変な…
You're giving the women in my family the wrong idea!
I thought you might not realize it was from me unless I used some sort of distinctive style.
何かアクセントがないと
私からって
気づいてもらえないかと思って
Use your name like everyone else!
普通に名前書いてください
で　バイトの指導役の人って？
So, who's going to be my trainer?
Me, of course.
私だけど　もちろん
それじゃ
Bye.
Want me to kiss you?
唇　奪われたいのかな？
（千鶴）さてと…　ほんじゃ
何かあったら携帯で呼んでね
Now...
Call my cell if you need help.
はい
Okay.
（タマ）ご精が出ますねい　ダンナ
Working hard, Master?
まあな
Yeah.
It's very noble of you, earning money secretly to fix the statue.
修理代をこっそり
寄付しようなんて
殊勝な心がけじゃないすか
地蔵様もきっと
呪いを和らげてくれますって
I'm sure the statue will go easy on you about the curse.
（くまねこ）
和らげてくれますって
Yes, it will.
だと　いいけど
I hope so.
Let's see, the next address is...
えっと　次の配達先はと…
≪（加奈子）おい潤平
おめえもバイトか？
Hey Junpei, you found a job too?
すッ　住吉　何で？
S-Sumiyoshi!
Why?!
ああ？　女子高生は
いろいろ金がかかんだよ
High school girls need lots of stuff!
服だろ　コスメだろ
新しい携帯だろ
Like clothes, cosmetics, a new cell phone, and considering the season...
それに　この時期は…
あッ　ひょっとしてお前
気持ちを誠意で示すってヤツ？
Hey, you're showing your feelings through dedication?
Did she overhear the deal about the statue?
〈こいつ　まさか
こないだの猫地蔵の話を…〉
クリスマスプレゼントなら
遠慮なくもらってやるぜ
I'll gladly accept a Christmas present from you, in return for all the help I've given you.
いつも面倒見てやってっからな
〈何だ　バレたわけじゃねえのか〉
Oh, it wasn't about that.
≪（加奈子）そっか～　そんなに
私に　ご奉仕したいか→
I see. You want to be my servant that badly?
何にしよっかな～　うーん
What should I ask for?
ちげーよ
Hell no.
口の利き方に気いつけろ
お前は私の下僕…
Watch your mouth!
You're my servant—
いつまでもガキみてえなこと
言ってんじゃねえっつーの
Stop talking like a kid already.
Anyway, I need to get back to my deliveries.
じゃ俺　配達あっから
あッ　てめえ
Damn you!
待て　コラーッ！
Wait!
〈んだよ　あんにゃろー
ツンケンしやがって〉
What's with his attitude?
住吉さん　笑顔　笑顔
Sumiyoshi-san, smile, smile!
あッ　ありがとうございました
Th-Thank you very much.
（客）はい　ありがとう
Thank you too.
よかったら休憩行ってきなよ
You can take a break.
私　さっき休んできたし
I took mine earlier.
Oh, okay.
ああ…　はい
クリスマスかあ
Christmas, huh...
≪（ＯＬ１）イブ　どうすんの？
What are your plans for Christmas Eve?
（ＯＬ２）
主任に誘われてんだけど～
The section manager asked me out.
（ＯＬ１）マジで？
Seriously?
Maybe I'll go just for the present.
プレゼントだけ　もらっとこうかな
あいつ金だけは持ってるからさ～
After all, he's rolling in dough.
…って潤平のヤツ　まさか
Maybe Junpei is planning to give K-Kaede a Christmas present and confess his feelings!
楓にクリスマスプレゼント渡して
ついに告る気じゃーッ！？
よっこいしょ…
よお　楓
カナちゃん
Hey, Kaede.
Kana-chan!
ナギー先輩達は？
Where are Nagi-senpai and the others?
ああ　うん
他の子達と一緒にランニング
They're all out running together.
（加奈子）そっか　ちょうどよかった
I see. Great timing.
うん？
差し入れ　一緒に食おうぜ
I brought this.
Let's eat it together.
Thank you! It looks good!
ありがとう　いただきまーす！
うーん　甘～ッ
So sweet.
あのさ　楓
うん？
H-Hey, Kaede...
クッ　クッ　クリスマスって
何してんの？
Wh-Wh-What are your plans for Christmas?
別に部活だよ
I'll be busy with the club.
終わったあと　みんなで
お茶ぐらいすると思うけど…
We might go out for some tea after practice though.
だッ　だよな？
I-I thought so!
〈よかった～　まあ　あいつに
んな度胸あるわけねえし〉
G-Good.
Of course, he'd never have the guts to do that.
でも　おいしいね　このケーキ
This cake's delicious.
おッ　おう　よかった
Y-Yeah...
That's good.
I never have any luck baking cakes.
私ね　昔から　ケーキだけは
うまく焼けないんだよ
他の料理は大丈夫なんだけどさ
I can cook anything else just fine.
I'm sorry, Kaede.
〈ゴメン　楓　私ホントは
やっぱ　あのバカのこと…〉
The truth is, about that idiot... I still...
うわッ　おやめくださーい！
Please stop!
よいではないか　ニョホホホホホッ
What's wrong?
仕事終わったとたん
ソッコー　お代官すか
You go wild as soon as you get off work?
やだなあ　潤平君の歓迎会よ～
Oh come on, it's just to welcome you.
テメー　私のドリンクバーが
飲めねえってのか？
Or are you saying you won't drink what I buy?!
I wanna go home.
もう　帰りたい
ていうか　みんなレベル高え
おもしろすぎ
Everyone's so good at this.
They're way too funny.
俺が誰かに似てる？　それは幻想だ
I look like someone else?!
That's an illusion! Stop that bullshit illu—
その　ふざけた幻想をブチ…
ごめんね　潤平君　ゆうべは
I'm sorry about last night, Junpei-kun.
ホントすよ
じゃあ　またあとで
Seriously.
See ya.
さてと…
Now...
あの頃は　よかったよな～
We had great times back then.
何も考えねえで　はしゃいでられて
We could have fun without a care in the world.
行ってきまーす
I'm off.
よお　今からバイト？
Hey, are you going to work?
まあな
Y-Yeah.
それ　ウチにか？
あッ　ああ
Are they for me?
Y-Yeah.
ボサッと突っ立ってねえで
さっさとよこせよ　オラッ
Then don't just stand there, give them to me!
10 Promises Between
Me & My Cat
おッ　そっか　これ当たったのか
Oh hey, I won.
It looks like a cheesy flick.
ベタくせえ映画だけど
お前そんなの見んの？
You like that kind of stuff?
たまたまだよ　こないだ
懸賞サイトで募集してて
I-It was just luck!
I won it on a giveaway website by sheer luck.
そうだ
おめえ　この日　バイトって？
Hey, are you working that day?
休みだけど？
そーか　そーか
I'm off.
Oh, yeah?
I need to go to the next...
俺　次の配達が…
じゃあ　３時にサンロードの
入り口で待ち合わせな
Then let's meet at 3:00 at the entrance of Sun Road.
I'll whack you a hundred times if you cry during the movie.
もし　映画みて泣いたら
百たたきの刑だ
You'd better be prepared.
覚悟しとけ
Y-Yes.
はい…
Why did she have to force this on me?
…ったく　住吉のヤロー
無理やり押しつけやがって
Stare...
ジーーッ
んだよ　ジーーッて
What are you looking at?
何か言いたいことでも
あんのかよ
You got something to say?
No.
別に　ただ私もあの子とは一応
古いつきあいだからさ
But you know, I've also been with her a long time.
何年もケンカ別れしてたものが
また　つるむようになったんだ
You're finally together again after fighting and breaking up.
Stop complaining and be good to her.
ブツクサ言わず
昔みたいに仲良くしておやり
フン
Jeez!
もう！
パラパラ漫画　よれたでしょう！
You messed up my doodling!
なにごと？
ちょっと探し物があってな
What's going on?
I'm looking for something.
エッチな本ですか
Your nudie mags?
どうしてお前は
すぐそっちの方へ！
What makes you suggest that?!
I'm worried about your future!
お兄ちゃんは
お前の将来が心配です
It's none of your business.
大きなお世話！
遅えな　潤平のヤツ
He's taking so long.
〈いかん
ついやらかしてしまった〉
Crap, now I've done it.
〈クリスマスまで
まだ数日あるとはいえ〉
Everyone's full of Christmas spirit, even though it's still a few days away.
〈街は　このムード〉
I might get carried away and...
〈雰囲気に流されて…〉
I... I...
こッ　こッ
告っちまうかもしれねーーッ！
I might confess to him!
おう　どうした？　デカイ声出して
What was that scream about?
いやッ　そのッ
No, nothing!
ずいぶん余裕じゃねえか　おい
You're quite relaxed, huh?
だりくてよ
ここんとこ毎日バイトしてっから
I'm just tired from working every day.
≪（加奈子）そうか　そうか
Oh, yeah?
…って
ちっとはシャレこいて来い！
And dress a little better!
Come on, let's get going!
オラ　行くぞ
Hey, ow! Ow!
おいおい　映画じゃねえのか？
Hey, aren't we going to a movie?
Don't worry.
いいだろ　時間あっし
ちょっとブラブラしてこーぜ
We have time to kill, so let's take a stroll.
Um, Miss Sumiyoshi, will I be buying this with my wages?
あの～　住吉さん
まさかこれ　俺のバイト代で？
うん？　さあね
Who knows?
ちょッ　今　笑ってたろ
I don't like that grin!
Does this look good on me?
似合うか？
どうだ？　うん？
Well?
馬子にも衣装？
Fine feathers make fine birds, I guess.
テメー　どの口が言った？　オラッ
You piece of crap!
Please!
お客様！
I'm so tired...
疲れたー
うーん　オレンジペコーの香りが
優雅な休日のひとときを
The fragrance of orange pekoe adds
a gentle color to an elegant afternoon.
優しく彩ってくれるわ
And it's cold.
しかも　さみい
何で真冬にオープンカフェ？
Why an outdoor café during winter?
Shut up! I just read about it in a magazine!
うるせーよ　雑誌で見たのッ
Don't you see how fancy this is?
わっかんねーかな
このシャレこきっぷり
オーホッホッホッホ！
Yeah, yeah, all right.
はいはい　さいですか
I'm sure—
どーせ…
This way.
こっちだぞ
O-Oh, it's just a rich woman.
何だ　シロガネーゼか
都心は　まったく油断ならねーぜ
Man, I need to be careful in the metro area.
ハハハハッ
シロガネーゼって今言わねえか
D-Did I just say "a rich woman"?
どうした？　住吉
What's up, Sumiyoshi?
It's nothing.
いや　何でもねえよ
I'm sorry, Kaede, I...
〈ごめん　楓　私…〉
おッ　前　進んだぞ
Hey, the line's moving.
〈裏切ってるよな　お前を〉
I'm betraying you.
試写状をお見せください
May I see your tickets?
ああ　はい
Here.
Oh, this too.
ああ　これ
H-Hey, why?
あッ　お前　何で？
何でって　ほら
Why? See.
We'll be giving away special cat-themed cell straps to anyone who brings cat-related items.
≪（加奈子）「当日猫グッズを
お持ちの方には特製ストラップをプレゼント」
I told you I didn't give it away.
前に言ったろ　あげてねえって
お願いします
はい
Is this okay?
Yes.
こちら記念品になります
Here's your souvenir.
どうも
Thanks.
ほれ
Here.
Don't just stand there.
ボーッとしてんなよ
あと　つっかえてっぞ
People are waiting behind you.
Y-Yeah.
おッ　おう
≪（ハルミ）「パパが倒れた？」
Dad's sick?
≪（母親）「ええ　ウチの大学病院に
しばらく入院…」
Yes, and he'll be in the university hospital for a while.
Figures.
〈そうだよな　ガキん頃から
このバカ　ヘタレで意地っ張りで〉
He was always useless and stubborn.
（ハルミ）「ああ～ッ？」
「ニャーン」
I see.
You found a cat?
〈でも　そのくせ
困ってるやつを見ると〉
But he could never ignore people in need.
〈ほうっておけなくて〉
I made ten promises to the cat.
〈泣き虫なとこも　あの頃と
ちっとも変わっちゃいねえ〉
He cries easily too, just like back then.
East Tokiwa Park
《（せきこむ潤平）》
A-Are you all right, Junpei?
《大丈夫か？　潤平》
《うん》
Y-Yeah.
《ごめんな　ニャム》
I'm sorry, Nyam.
I'm your owner, but I can't even touch you.
《俺　飼い主なのに
触ってやれなくて》
Don't worry!
《心配すんな　私が代わりに
いっぱいニャムと遊んでやっから》
I'll play with Nyam a lot on your behalf!
Yeah.
《でもよ…》
《任せろ》
But...
Just leave it to me!
《だから　もう
グズグズ泣くんじゃねえ》
So stop crying already.
《うん》
Yeah.
《≪（加奈子）うし　完成！》
Done!
《これなら潤平も
安心して触れるぜ→》
Junpei can touch this without a problem.
It'll be a sign of our friendship!
《これは　私らの友情の証しだ》
There's still so much I need to tell you!
（ハルミ）「私はまだ　お前に
話したいことがいっぱいあるの」
Yes, you do.
いっぱいあるの…
〈ああ～　やっぱ告んのナシかな
うん〉
I guess I won't confess to him today.
So I want you to stay with me.
〈今は　ただ　このバカの隣に
いられりゃいいや〉
I'll be happy if I can just stay by his side...
〈ダチとして〉
as his friend.
The movie was so-so.
まあまあの映画だったな
You cry way too much!
つうか　泣きすぎで引くわ
マジで百たたきの刑にすっぞ
I'll whack you a hundred times for real!
まあ　これは
ありがたくもらっといてやる
Anyway, I'll keep this.
だから　お前もそれ
大事に持っとけよ
So you'd better take good care of that doll.
捨てねえで　ずっと
Don't ever throw it away.
Y-Yeah.
おッ　おう
じゃあな　潤平
See ya, Junpei.
おッ　おう
Y-Yeah.
住吉のヤツ
結局いろいろ　おごらせやがって
She ended up making me pay for so much.
何だったんだ？　一体
What's up with her?
You dimwit!
この罰当たりめッ
猫パンチ！　猫キック！→
Cat punch!
Cat kick!
I still remember my old skills!
昔取ったきねづか
私だって　やるときゃやるよ
Now, next...
さてと　次は…
There you are!
いた～～ッ！　助けてほしいの
Please help us!
Merry Christmas!
≪（加奈子）メリークリスマス！
ありがとっ　した～！
Thank you very much.
Kana-chan.
カ～ナちゃん
おう　楓
H-Hey, Kaede.
ケーキ買いにきたよ
I came to buy a cake.
おう　あれか？　部活中か？
O-Oh, still practicing?
Yeah.
うん　休憩に先輩達と一緒に
食べようと思って
I want to share one with my teammates during our break.
ほら　おごりだ　持ってけ
Here.
It's on me. Take it.
でも…
But...
Sorry, Kaede.
悪かったな　楓
何が？
For what?
１つ　いただけます？
May I have one?
ああ　ごめん
いらっしゃいませ
Sorry.
Welcome!
≪（客）このイチゴのやつを
（加奈子）はい
I'll take the strawberry one.
Okay.
どうしたのかな？　カナちゃん
I wonder what's bothering Kana-chan.
あれ？
Oh?
高坂君？
Kousaka-kun?
ニャ～ッ！　ニャ～ッ！
Come on, jump!
ほら　飛び降りろって
怖くねえから
Don't be scared!
ニャーッ
たく　世話かけやがって
Man, this is such a hassle!
高坂君
Kousaka-kun!
Well, I hope this will lift the curse a bit.
まッ　これで少しは
ゆるくなってくれっかな
呪い
〈呪い？〉
The curse?
ニャ～ッ　ニャ～ッ
いや　お礼とかいいから
No, really, no need to thank me.
ネズミとか持ってこられても
困るし
I really have no use for rats.
He said something about a curse once before,
〈呪いって　そういえば前にも…〉
〈それに高坂君　何だか
まるで猫と話してるみたい〉
and it looks like he's talking with the cats.
いっけね　バイトに戻んねえと
Shoot, I'd better get back to work!
まさか…　ね
No way...
お帰り～　お茶にしよっか
Good work.
Want some tea?
ういーっす
Thanks.
あれ？　おかしいな
Weird.
近くに猫なんか…
There aren't any cats around here.
No freakin' way!
嘘でしょ～～ッ！？
natsu no kaze kirameku machi ni
In this town where the wind sparkles,
nigemizu oikakeru anata no sugata
I see you chasing a mirage.
shinkokyuu shite oikakeru kedo
You take a deep breath and keep chasing it.
chiisaku kieteyuku senaka ni sotto tsubuyaita
I whisper to your back as you get further away.
nemurenai yoru ni me wo tojite
When I close my eyes on sleepless nights,
omoiegaku mirai niwa
and imagine my future,
futari no egao sore igai ni mou mienai
I can only see the two of us smiling together.
konnani setsunai kimochi
This really sweet, painful thought...
kizuite kurenakutemo
Even if you never notice it,
kokoro ni sotto negau dake
I just wish for it in my mind.
ashita ni nareba kanau hazu!
I'm sure it'll come true tomorrow!
surechigatta shunkan ni
At the moment we passed by each other,
waraikakete kureta ne
you gave me a smile.
soredake de mune ga atsui
Just that makes my heart glow,
shiawase dakara
because I'm happy...
because I'm happy.
Strawberry Tears
Strawberry tears.
Today's Nyan Koma.
Today's Nyan Koma
まさかネコ耳とは…
こんなところを誰かに見られたら
I've got cat ears!
What if someone sees me like this?
≪（晴彦）や～　朝イチで
並んだかいがあったさ
It was really worth getting in line early this morning.
やっぱネコ耳娘の特典つけられちゃ
見逃すわけには…
I couldn't miss it now that they've added extra cat-eared girls.
見逃すわけにはいかないよね～
見逃して
No way I could miss it!
Please miss it.
果たしてダンナの運命や　いかに
Nyan Koma
What will become of Master?
ちなみに私達の耳は
片方ずつ別々に動かせるよ
By the way, we can move our ears independently.
Now, next week is the final episode!
No good.
Too strange.
Senpai hasn't done anything for so long.
I wonder what that was about yesterday.
The curse of the cat statue...
Why bother worrying?
Curses can't be real.
But Kousaka-kun always...
Always what?
We need to clear up Mizuno's misunderstanding as soon as possible.
Thank you, Kousaka-kun. I...
Next Nyan Koi, the final episode, 12th nyan-ko,
"Can Heaven Wait?"
So this really is where I end up!